http://www.castclassics.com/privacy-policy.html

Menu
StylesContemporaryAero AxiomAxiom WovenContinuum (Quick Ship)Coronado (Quick Ship)MagnusVector (Quick Ship)TransitionalAxiom WovenContinuum (Quick Ship)Coronado (Quick Ship)Fortuna (Quick Ship)MagnusMirageMonte Cristo (Quick Ship)Sutton Sling (Quick Ship)TraditionalMirageMonte Cristo (Quick Ship)Mid CenturyContinuumCortinaFortunaPresidioSoarSuttonSutton SlingCollectionsCushionAeroAxiom (Quick Ship)CortinaMagnusMirageMonte Cristo (Quick Ship)OlympusPresidio (Quick Ship)SlingAeroContinuum (Quick Ship)Cornado (Quick Ship)SoarSutton Sling (Quick Ship)Vector Sling (Quick Ship)MixedAxiom WovenFortuna (Quick Ship)SuttonTablesTable TopsAuraRoadsterSolaireTable BasesCasaCoastVectorComplete TableKingsportNorthportOpusWestportFirepitsCushionsCustomer CareAbout UsCare and MaintenanceContact USDownload CatalogMeet The DesignerPaymentShowroom TourWarrantyDesign CenterFabricsFrameWeaveStore Locator
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
CAST CLASSICS
Privacy Policy:
Thank you for visiting www.castclassics.com, (herein referred to as the “Site”), and for reviewing our Privacy Policy.
The server on which this “site” is located collects and saves only default information customarily logged by web server software. This may be the originating IP address, the time and day you visited the “Site”, and the pages and images you requested.
The privacy and protection of your information is of utmost importance to us. We do not and will not make any of your identifiable information available to a third party. We will not sell or give away any of your information. Cast Classics may use this information internally from time to time in order to study the sites accessibility and make improvements towards a more user-friendly environment.
This Privacy Policy is a contract that is written under and will be governed by the Laws of the State of New Jersey.
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless the website, its members, managers, officers, affiliates, agents and employees, from and against any and all loss, expense, attorney fees and expenses, costs, damages, claims, and any other liability related to or associated with your use of this“site” and any violation of Cast Classics’ Privacy Policy.
Should you have any questions regarding this ”site” and or this privacy policy please send an e-mail to info@castclassics.com .
